Hi, I'm excited to work with you on using networking to find more
嗨 我很高兴和大家一起讨论使用人际网络来寻找
work opportunities.
更多的工作机会
The more people you know, or the more presence you have online,
你认识的人越多 或者你的人际网络越广
the more likely you'll be able to find opportunities or
你就越有可能找到机会 或者
have opportunities find you.
有机会送上门来
I want to share a story with you.
我想跟你分享一个故事
The first time I networked was when I was 13 years old.
我第一次用到人际网络是在 13 岁时
I wanted to find an afterschool job as a babysitter.
我当时想在课余兼职做临时保姆
I asked my parents for advice.
我向父母寻求建议
They told me to look at the classified ads to see who was looking.
他们告诉我可以在报纸上的分类广告中找找看
To post flyers at my school to advertise.
或在学校张贴传单进行宣传
And to also ask my parents' coworkers if they knew anyone looking for
或者他们可以帮我问问同事 看是否有人知道
a babysitter.
谁家招保姆
I actually had a few people reach out after seeing my flyers.
之后的确有几个人看到我的传单并联系了我
But I got my first biggest in gig from my friend of my mom's co-worker.
但是我的第一份保姆工作是通过我妈妈的同事找到的
I've also used the same networking system whenever I search for a new job.
之后在找任何新工作时 我都使用了同样的人际网络系统
Nowadays, instead of using the classified section of the newspaper,
如今 我不再使用报纸上的分类广告栏
I search for opening on job works like Indeed and Dice.
而是通过一些求职网站 如 Indeed 和 Dice
Networking gave me access to more job works.
网络让我接触了更多的求职平台
I joined a lot of local professional groups which have their own job works,
我加入了一些当地职业团体 他们有自己的求职网站
not open to the general public.
但不对公众开放
After college, I moved across the country unemployed.
大学毕业后 我搬到了新的地方 当时还没有工作
And I got a job from a posting and a local group list serve.
我从一个帖子和一个本地团队服务名单获得了一份工作
For most of my career, I would say my LinkedIn profile was pretty bad,
在我大部分职业生涯中 我的领英个人资料都做得比较糟
because I didn't take it seriously.
因为我没有认真对待过
However, one day, I took the advice from Udacity's LinkedIn course, and
但是 有一天 我从优达学城的领英课程得到了建议
rebranded myself on my page.
并在我的网页上重塑了自己的形象
I got three emails from recruiters that week.
那一周我就获得了三份招聘者邮件
Those recruiters found me because I optimized my LinkedIn profile for
这些招聘者之所以能找到我 是因为我对自己的领英资料
searches.
做了搜索优化
And instead of asking my parents coworkers for
这次我不是通过父母的同事来获得
job leads, I attended meetups and mixers to connect with people in the industry.
职业线索 而是参加聚会和交谊会 在行业中建立了人际网络
And I have found job opportunities that way.
并通过这种方式找到了工作机会
I found my current job at Udacity through a conversation with someone
对于目前在优达学城的工作 我是在和一个从事技术行业的朋友聊天时
in the tech industry who I actually didn’t know all that well at the time.
得知这个机会的 而当时我和她甚至不是很熟悉
You don't know where opportunity will come from.
所以 有时候机会在你不知道的时候就来了
And the best way to make sure you don't miss out on opening,
那么要确保你不错过机会 最好的一个方式
is to have a great online presence and network.
是保持线上和线下的人际网络
In this lesson, we'll review how to network and
在这节课中 我们将讨论如何建立此网络
spend some time on personal branding,
并花一些时间进行个人营销
which will make sure your networking attempts lead to job opportunities.
这会帮助你将网络力量变为工作机会